Chip Py Go-Go Collection 199
People's Archive, MLK Library
Chip Py Go-Go Collection
2010-2020
People's Archive, MLK Library
Py, Chip
199
15.3 Gigabytes 1,979 files; DIG_0029
Arrangement
The Chip Py Go-Go Collection is arranged chronologically.
Biographical / Historical
A native to the D.C. area, Chip Py has been shooting the D.C. music scene since 2005 and the Go-Go scene since 2010. He became Chuck Brown's official photographer during the last year of the musician's life.
Custodial History
The collection was transferred to DC Public Library in 2020 by Chip Py.
Content Description
The Chip Py Go-Go Collection consists of 1,900-plus individually composed and artistically rendered images of concert performances of Chuck Brown, the 'Godfather of Go-Go'; and other individuals and bands, including Rare Essence, Backyard Band, Familiar Faces, Suttle Thoughts, BE'LA DONA, and Da Mixx. The photographs were taken by Chip Py, personal photographer to Chuck Brown, between 2010 and 2020. The bulk of the collection dates from 2010-2014. The collection documents the importance of this unique music genre, which became the official music of Washington, D.C. February 19, 2020. As much as possible, each image includes the musicians' stage and given names, band names, and the date and venue of the performances. Whenever possible, band names, stage names, and venues names were taken from sources created by the performers.
Go-go (Music); Digital materials; Music; Black people; African Americans
- Series 1: Photographs, 2011-2020; 199chippy
  - Chuck Brown headlining with Chuck Brown Band at the 2010 National Capital Barbecue Battle, 2010-06-26; 199chippy_0001; Chuck Brown while performing with Chuck Brown Band at the 2010 National Capital Barbecue Battle on the National Mall between 9th and 14th Street, NW. He flashes a thumbs up to the camera.
  - Chuck Brown headlining with Chuck Brown Band at the 2010 National Capital Barbecue Battle, 2010-06-26; 199chippy_0002; Chuck Brown playing electric guitar while performing with Chuck Brown Band at the 2010 National Capital Barbecue Battle on the National Mall between 9th and 14th Street, NW.
  - Chuck Brown headlining with Chuck Brown Band at the 2010 National Capital Barbecue Battle, 2010-06-26; 199chippy_0003; Chuck Brown playing electric guitar while performing with Chuck Brown Band at the 2010 National Capital Barbecue Battle on the National Mall between 9th and 14th Street, NW.
  - Chuck Brown headlining with Chuck Brown Band at the 2010 National Capital Barbecue Battle, 2010-06-26; 199chippy_0004; Chuck Brown toweling off his face while performing with Chuck Brown Band at the 2010 National Capital Barbecue Battle on the National Mall between 9th and 14th Street, NW.
  - Chuck Brown headlining with Chuck Brown Band at the 2010 National Capital Barbecue Battle, 2010-06-26; 199chippy_0005; Chuck Brown playing electric guitar while performing with Chuck Brown Band at the 2010 National Capital Barbecue Battle on the National Mall between 9th and 14th Street, NW.
  - Ms Kim performing with Chuck Brown Band at the 2010 National Capital Barbecue Battle, 2010-06-26; 199chippy_0006; Ms Kim performing with Chuck Brown Band at the 2010 National Capital Barbecue Battle on the National Mall between 9th and 14th Street, NW.
  - Ms Kim performing with Chuck Brown Band at the 2010 National Capital Barbecue Battle, 2010-06-26; 199chippy_0007; Ms Kim performing with Chuck Brown Band at the 2010 National Capital Barbecue Battle on the National Mall between 9th and 14th Street, NW.
  - Ms Kim performing with Chuck Brown Band at the 2010 National Capital Barbecue Battle, 2010-06-26; 199chippy_0008; Ms Kim performing with Chuck Brown Band at the 2010 National Capital Barbecue Battle on the National Mall between 9th and 14th Street, NW.
  - Ms Kim performing with Chuck Brown Band at the 2010 National Capital Barbecue Battle, 2010-06-26; 199chippy_0009; Ms Kim performing with Chuck Brown Band at the 2010 National Capital Barbecue Battle on the National Mall between 9th and 14th Street, NW.
  - Ms Kim performing with Chuck Brown Band at the 2010 National Capital Barbecue Battle, 2010-06-26; 199chippy_0010; Ms Kim performing with Chuck Brown Band at the 2010 National Capital Barbecue Battle on the National Mall between 9th and 14th Street, NW.
  - Ms Kim performing with Chuck Brown Band at the 2010 National Capital Barbecue Battle, 2010-06-26; 199chippy_0011; Ms Kim performing with Chuck Brown Band at the 2010 National Capital Barbecue Battle on the National Mall between 9th and 14th Street, NW. Chuck Brown is visible in the background.
  - Chuck Brown headlining with Chuck Brown Band at the 2010 National Capital Barbecue Battle, 2010-06-26; 199chippy_0012; Chuck Brown playing electric guitar while performing with Chuck Brown Band at the 2010 National Capital Barbecue Battle on the National Mall between 9th and 14th Street, NW.
  - Ms Kim performing with Chuck Brown Band at the 2010 National Capital Barbecue Battle, 2010-06-26; 199chippy_0013; Ms Kim performing with Chuck Brown Band at the 2010 National Capital Barbecue Battle on the National Mall between 9th and 14th Street, NW. Chuck Brown is visible in the background.
  - KK towels off Chuck Brown while performing with Chuck Brown Band at the 2010 National Capital Barbecue Battle, 2010-06-26; 199chippy_0014; KK towels off Chuck Brown while performing with Chuck Brown Band at the 2010 National Capital Barbecue Battle on the National Mall between 9th and 14th Street, NW.
  - Sweet Cherie performing with Chuck Brown Band at the Workhouse Arts Center, 2010-09-04; 199chippy_0034; Sweet Cherie playing the electronic keyboard while performing with Chuck Brown Band at the Workhouse Arts Center.
  - Sweet Cherie performing with Chuck Brown Band at the Workhouse Arts Center, 2010-09-04; 199chippy_0035; Sweet Cherie playing the electronic keyboard while performing with Chuck Brown Band at the Workhouse Arts Center.
  - Ms Kim performing with Chuck Brown Band at the Workhouse Arts Center, 2010-09-04; 199chippy_0036; Ms Kim performing with Chuck Brown Band at the Workhouse Arts Center. A tambourine is in her right hand.
  - Sweet Cherie performing with Chuck Brown Band at the Workhouse Arts Center, 2010-09-04; 199chippy_0037; Sweet Cherie playing the electronic keyboard while performing with Chuck Brown Band at the Workhouse Arts Center.
  - Mighty Moe performing with Chuck Brown Band at the Workhouse Arts Center, 2010-09-04; 199chippy_0038; Mighty Moe plays the bongos while performing with Chuck Brown Band at the Workhouse Arts Center. An unidentified performer is behind him.
  - Ms Kim performing with Chuck Brown Band at the Workhouse Arts Center, 2010-09-04; 199chippy_0039; Ms Kim performing with Chuck Brown Band at the Workhouse Arts Center.
  - Ms Kim performing with Chuck Brown Band at the Workhouse Arts Center, 2010-09-04; 199chippy_0040; Ms Kim shakes a cabasa in her right hand while performing with Chuck Brown Band at the Workhouse Arts Center.
  - D. Floyd performing with Chuck Brown Band at the Workhouse Arts Center, 2010-09-04; 199chippy_0041; D. Floyd performing with Chuck Brown Band at the Workhouse Arts Center.
  - D. Floyd performing with Chuck Brown Band at the Workhouse Arts Center, 2010-09-04; 199chippy_0042; D. Floyd performing with Chuck Brown Band at the Workhouse Arts Center.
  - Kwick Foot performing with Chuck Brown Band at the Workhouse Arts Center, 2010-09-04; 199chippy_0043; Kwick Foot gestures for camera while performing with Chuck Brown Band at the Workhouse Arts Center.
  - Chuck Brown performing with Chuck Brown Band at the Workhouse Arts Center, 2010-09-04; 199chippy_0044; Chuck Brown performing with Chuck Brown Band at the Workhouse Arts Center.
  - Chuck Brown performing with Chuck Brown Band at the Workhouse Arts Center, 2010-09-04; 199chippy_0045; Chuck Brown performing with Chuck Brown Band at the Workhouse Arts Center.
  - Child sits on man's shoulders watching Chuck Brown Band, 2010-09-04; 199chippy_0046; Child sits on man's shoulders watching Chuck Brown Band while man holds up cell phone.
  - KK and Greg Boyer performing with Chuck Brown Band at the Workhouse Arts Center, 2010-09-04; 199chippy_0047; KK performing with Chuck Brown Band at the Workhouse Arts Center with Greg Boyer playing an AMREIN trombone in background.
  - KK and Greg Boyer performing with Chuck Brown Band at the Workhouse Arts Center, 2010-09-04; 199chippy_0048; KK performing with Chuck Brown Band at the Workhouse Arts Center with Greg Boyer playing an AMREIN trombone in background.
  - KK and Greg Boyer performing with Chuck Brown Band at the Workhouse Arts Center, 2010-09-04; 199chippy_0049; KK performs on tambourine with Chuck Brown Band at the Workhouse Arts Center with Greg Boyer playing an AMREIN trombone in background.
  - Sharli McQueen performing with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue, 2010-09-09; 199chippy_0015; Sharli McQueen performing with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue.
  - Sugar Rai performing with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue, 2010-09-09; 199chippy_0016; Sugar Rai performing with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue. A tambourine is in her right hand.
  - Sugar Rai performing with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue, 2010-09-09; 199chippy_0017; Sugar Rai performing with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue. A tambourine is in her right hand.
  - Sugar Rai performing with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue, 2010-09-09; 199chippy_0018; Sugar Rai performing with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue.
  - Sugar Rai performing with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue, 2010-09-09; 199chippy_0019; Sugar Rai performing with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue.
  - Sugar Rai performing with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue, 2010-09-09; 199chippy_0020; Sugar Rai performing with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue in front of fans.
  - Sugar Rai performing with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue, 2010-09-09; 199chippy_0021; Sugar Rai performing with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue in front of fans.
  - Sharli McQueen performing with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue, 2010-09-09; 199chippy_0022; Sharli McQueen performing with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue.
  - Sugar Rai performing with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue, 2010-09-09; 199chippy_0023; Sugar Rai performing with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue. A tambourine is in her right hand.
  - Sugar Rai performing with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue, 2010-09-09; 199chippy_0024; Sugar Rai performing with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue. A tambourine is in her right hand.
  - Sugar Rai performing with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue, 2010-09-09; 199chippy_0025; Sugar Rai performing with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue. A tambourine is in her right hand.
  - Sugar Rai performing with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue, 2010-09-09; 199chippy_0026; Sugar Rai performing with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue. A tambourine is in her right hand.
  - Sugar Rai performing with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue, 2010-09-09; 199chippy_0027; Sugar Rai performing with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue. A tambourine is in her right hand.
  - Sugar Rai performing with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue, 2010-09-09; 199chippy_0028; Sugar Rai performing with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue. A tambourine is in her right hand.
  - Sharli McQueen performing with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue, 2010-09-09; 199chippy_0029; Sharli McQueen performing with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue.
  - Sharli McQueen performing with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue, 2010-09-09; 199chippy_0030; Sharli McQueen performing with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue.
  - Genny Jam performing with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue, 2010-09-09; 199chippy_0031; Genny Jam plays electric guitar while performing with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue. She holds guitar pick in her right hand. On her guitar strap is a pink breast cancer ribbon.
  - Sugar Bear and Kool Keys performing with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue, 2010-09-09; 199chippy_0032; Sugar Bear and Kool Keys performing with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue. Genny Jam and Shannon Browne are in the background.
  - Go-Go fan at the La Fontaine Bleue, 2010-09-09; 199chippy_0033; A Go-Go fan dances while holding a drink at the La Fontaine Bleue.
  - Killer Cal speaks at the 2010 Go-Go Awards and Hall of Fame Induction at Lincoln Theatre, 2010-11-21; 199chippy_0050; Killa Cal speaks during the 2010 Go-Go Awards and Hall of Fame Induction at the Lincoln theater.
  - Ms Kim performs at the 2010 Go-Go Awards and Hall of Fame Induction at Lincoln Theatre, 2010-11-21; 199chippy_0051; Ms Kim performs at the 2010 Go-Go Awards and Hall of Fame Induction with Councilmember Vincent Gray in background.
  - Genny Jam performs at the 2010 Go-Go Awards and Hall of Fame Induction at Lincoln Theatre, 2010-11-21; 199chippy_0052; Genny Jam plays an electric guitar on electric guitar at the 2010 Go-Go Awards and Hall of Fame Induction at the Lincoln theater. She holds a guitar pick in her right hand and her guitar strap features a pink breast cancer ribbon.
  - Genny Jam performs at the 2010 Go-Go Awards and Hall of Fame Induction, 2010-11-21; 199chippy_0053; Genny Jam plays an electric guitar on electric guitar at the 2010 Go-Go Awards and Hall of Fame Induction at the Lincoln theater. She holds a guitar pick in her right hand and her guitar strap features a pink breast cancer ribbon.
  - Genny Jam performs at the 2010 Go-Go Awards and Hall of Fame Induction, 2010-11-21; 199chippy_0054; Genny Jam plays an electric guitar on electric guitar at the 2010 Go-Go Hall of Fame Awards at the Lincoln theater.
  - Sweet Cherie performs at the 2010 Go-Go Awards and Hall of Fame Induction, 2010-11-21; 199chippy_0055; Sweet Cherie performs at the 2010 Go-Go Awards and Hall of Fame Induction at the Lincoln theater.
  - Sharli McQueen performs with BE'LA DONA at the 2010 Go-Go Awards and Hall of Fame Induction, 2010-11-21; 199chippy_0056; Sharli McQueen performs as Party of BE'LA DONA for the 2010 Go-Go Awards and Hall of Fame Induction at the Lincoln theater.
  - Sharli McQueen performs with BE'LA DONA at the 2010 Go-Go Awards and Hall of Fame Induction, 2010-11-21; 199chippy_0057; Sharli McQueen performs as Party of BE'LA DONA for the 2010 Go-Go Awards and Hall of Fame Induction at the Lincoln theater.
  - Sharli McQueen performs with BE'LA DONA at the 2010 Go-Go Awards and Hall of Fame Induction, 2010-11-21; 199chippy_0058; Sharli McQueen performs as Party of BE'LA DONA for the 2010 Go-Go Music Awards and Hall of Fame Induction at the Lincoln theater.
  - Ms Kim and Kwick Foot accept award at the 2010 Go-Go Awards and Hall of Fame Induction, 2010-11-21; 199chippy_0059; Ms Kim and Kwick Foot accept award at the 2010 Go-Go Music Awards and Hall of Fame Induction at the Lincoln theater.
  - Ms Kim, Kwick Foot, and KK accept award at the 2010 Go-Go Awards and Hall of Fame Induction, 2010-11-21; 199chippy_0060; Ms Kim, Kwick Foot, and KK accept award at the 2010 Go-Go Music Awards and Hall of Fame Induction at the Lincoln theater.
  - Uno Boss and Ms Kim at the 2010 Go-Go Awards and Hall of Fame Induction with Ms Kim, 2010-11-21; 199chippy_0061; Uno Boss speaks with Ms Kim at the 2010 Go-Go Music Awards and Hall of Fame Induction at the Lincoln theater.
  - Unknown performer gestures with a fist at the 2010 Go-Go Awards and Hall of Fame Induction, 2010-11-21; 199chippy_0062; Unknown performer gestures with a fist at the 2010 Go-Go Music Awards and Hall of Fame Induction at the Lincoln theater.
  - Sugar Bear and Chuck Brown accept an award at the 2010 Go-Go Awards and Hall of Fame Induction, 2010-11-21; 199chippy_0063; Sugar Bear speaks with Chuck Brown at the 2010 Go-Go Awards and Hall of Fame Induction at the Lincoln theater.
  - Chuck Brown speaks at the 2010 Go-Go Awards and Hall of Fame Induction, 2010-11-21; 199chippy_0064; Chuck Brown speaks at the 2010 Go-Go Awards and Hall of Fame Induction at the Lincoln theater.
  - Unknown performer at the 2010 Go-Go Awards and Hall of Fame Induction, 2010-11-21; 199chippy_0065; Unknown performer looks into distance with sunglasses on at the 2010 Go-Go Music Awards and Hall of Fame Induction at the Lincoln theater.
  - Ms Kim smiles during 2010 Go-Go Awards and Hall of Fame Induction, 2010-11-21; 199chippy_0066; Ms Kim smiles during the 2010 Go-Go Awards and Hall of Fame Induction at the Lincoln theater.
  - Frank 'Scooby' Sirius: the Godson of Go-Go performs during the 2010 Go-Go Awards and Hall of Fame Induction, 2010-11-21; 199chippy_0067; Frank 'Scooby' Sirius: the Godson of Go-Go performs during the 2010 Go-Go Awards and Hall of Fame Induction at the Lincoln theater.
  - Ms Kim performs at the 2010 Go-Go Awards and Hall of Fame Induction, 2010-11-21; 199chippy_0068; Ms Kim performs at the 2010 Go-Go Awards and Hall of Fame Induction.
  - KeKe performs with Rare Essence at the 2010 Go-Go Awards and Hall of Fame Induction, 2010-11-21; 199chippy_0069; KeKe performs with Rare Essence at the 2010 Go-Go Awards and Hall of Fame induction at the Lincoln theater.
  - Mz Laydee performs with DC Vybe at the 2010 Go-Go Awards and Hall of Fame Induction, 2010-11-21; 199chippy_0070; Mz Laydee performs with DC Vybe at the 2010 Go-Go Awards and Hall of Fame Induction at the Lincoln theater.
  - D. Floyd performs with Rare Essence at the 2010 Go-Go Awards and Hall of Fame Induction, 2010-11-21; 199chippy_0071; D. Floyd performs at the 2010 Go-Go Awards and Hall of Fame Induction at the Lincoln theater.
  - Whiteboy performs with Rare Essence at the 2010 Go-Go Awards and Hall of Fame Induction, 2010-11-21; 199chippy_0072; Whiteboy performs on electric guitar at the 2010 Go-Go Awards and Hall of Fame Induction at the Lincoln theater.
  - D. Floyd performs with Rare Essence at the 2010 Go-Go Awards and Hall of Fame Induction, 2010-11-21; 199chippy_0073; D. Floyd performs at the 2010 Go-Go Awards and Hall of Fame Induction at the Lincoln theater.
  - Shorty Corleone and KeKe perform with Rare Essence at the 2010 Go-Go Awards and Hall of Fame Induction, 2010-11-21; 199chippy_0074; Shorty Corleone and KeKe perform with Rare Essence at the 2010 Go-Go Awards and Hall of Fame Induction at the Lincoln theater.
  - Shorty Corleone and KeKe perform with Rare Essence at the 2010 Go-Go Awards and Hall of Fame Induction, 2010-11-21; 199chippy_0075; Shorty Corleone and KeKe perform with Rare Essence at the 2010 Go-Go Awards and Hall of Fame Induction at the Lincoln theater.
  - KeKe performs with Rare Essence at the 2010 Go-Go Awards and Hall of Fame Induction, 2010-11-21; 199chippy_0076; KeKe performs with Rare Essence at the 2010 Go-Go Awards and Hall of Fame Induction at the Lincoln theater.
  - Shorty Corleone performs with Rare Essence at the 2010 Go-Go Awards and Hall of Fame Induction, 2010-11-21; 199chippy_0077; Shorty Corleone performs at the 2010 Go-Go Awards and Hall of Fame Induction at the Lincoln theater.
  - KeKe and D. Floyd perform at the 2010 Go-Go Awards and Hall of Fame Induction, 2010-11-21; 199chippy_0078; KeKe and D. Floyd perform at the 2010 Go-Go Awards and Hall of Fame Induction at the Lincoln theater.
  - Go-Go Mickey performs with Rare Essence at the 2010 Go-Go Awards and Hall of Fame Induction, 2010-11-21; 199chippy_0079; Go-Go Mickey performs on bongos at the 2010 Go-Go Awards and Hall of Fame Induction at the Lincoln theater.
  - Genny Jam performs with BE'LA DONA at the 2010 Go-Go Awards and Hall of Fame Induction, 2010-11-21; 199chippy_0080; Genny Jam plays an electric guitar on electric guitar with Miss Karis in background at the 2010 Go-Go Awards and Hall of Fame Induction at the Lincoln theater.
  - Kim Scott performing with BE'LA DONA at the Go-Go Hall of Fame Awards, 2010-11-21; 199chippy_0081; Kim Scott of BE'LA DONA performing at the 2010 Go-Go Hall of Fame Awards.
  - Miss Karis performing with BE'LA DONA at the Go-Go Hall of Fame Awards, 2010-11-21; 199chippy_0082; Miss Karis of BE'LA DONA performing at the 2010 Go-Go Hall of Fame Awards.
  - Press coverage at the Go-Go Hall of Fame Awards, 2010-11-21; 199chippy_0083; A member of the press stands outside the Lincoln Theatre during the 2010 Go-Go Hall of Fame Awards.
  - Rare Essence performing at the Go-Go Hall of Fame Awards, 2010-11-21; 199chippy_0084; Members of Rare Essence perform at the 2010 Go-Go Hall of Fame Awards. Performers left to right are DP, D. Floyd on tenor saxophone, Shorty Corleone, and Ms Kim.
  - Genny Jam performing with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue, 2010-12-23; 199chippy_0085; Genny Jam plays electric guitar while performing with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue.
  - Miss Karis performing with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue, 2010-12-23; 199chippy_0086; Miss Karis performs with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue.
  - Miss Karis performing with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue, 2010-12-23; 199chippy_0087; Miss Karis performs with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue.
  - Sweet Cherie performing with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue, 2010-12-23; 199chippy_0088; Sweet Cherie plays the keys on a Korg Triton keyboard while performing with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue.
  - Sugar Rai and Miss Karis performing with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue, 2010-12-23; 199chippy_0089; From left to right Sugar Rai and Miss Karis perform with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue. Fans dance at the edge of the stage. In the background several musical instruments are visible.
  - Genny Jam and Miss Karis performing with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue, 2010-12-23; 199chippy_0090; From left to right Genny Jam plays electric guitar and Miss Karis sings while performing with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue.
  - Genny Jam and Miss Karis performing with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue, 2010-12-23; 199chippy_0091; From left to right Genny Jam and Miss Karis perform with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue. Genny Jam is playing an electric guitar.
  - Genny Jam and Miss Karis performing with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue, 2010-12-23; 199chippy_0092; From left to right Genny Jam and Miss Karis perform with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue. Genny Jam is playing an electric guitar. Other performers are visible in the background. A fan's hand reaching toward the stage is visible in the foreground.
  - Genny Jam and Miss Karis performing with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue, 2010-12-23; 199chippy_0093; From left to right Genny Jam and Miss Karis perform with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue. Genny Jam is playing an electric guitar.
  - Genny Jam and Miss Karis performing with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue, 2010-12-23; 199chippy_0094; From left to right Genny Jam and Miss Karis perform with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue. Genny Jam is playing an electric guitar. Fans dance at the edge of the stage.
  - Sugar Rai and Miss Karis performing with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue, 2010-12-23; 199chippy_0095; From left to right Sugar Rai with a tambourine over her right arm and Miss Karis perform with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue. In the background other performers are visible.
  - Miss Karis performing with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue, 2010-12-23; 199chippy_0096; Miss Karis performs with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue.
  - Sugar Rai performing with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue, 2010-12-23; 199chippy_0097; Sugar Rai performs with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue.
  - Miss Karis performing with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue, 2010-12-23; 199chippy_0098; Miss Karis performs with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue.
  - Sugar Rai and Miss Karis performing with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue, 2010-12-23; 199chippy_0099; From left to right Sugar Rai and Miss Karis perform with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue. In the background other performers are visible.
  - Sugar Rai and Miss Karis performing with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue, 2010-12-23; 199chippy_0100; From left to right Sugar Rai and Miss Karis perform with BE'LA DONA at La Fontaine Bleue. In the background other performers are visible.